### Adhan Nur

# Portfolio | LinkedIn | adhamnur147@gmail.com | 07414139595

#### **Summary**

Detail-oriented analytical thinker offering sharp time management, organizational, and research skills. I am a recent graduate with a BSc (Hons) in Psychology with placement, seeking an entry-level data analysis position. With five years of experience working in hospitality, I have a track record of achieving corporate objectives while delivering outstanding services, resulting in high customer satisfaction. Additionally, I have experiences in the clinical and research fields in Psychology.

#### **Skills**

Technical Skills: Excel (Formulas, Pivot tables, XLOOKUP, conditional formatting & data cleaning)

SQL, Python, Tableau & Power BI. Plus basic HTML & CSS

Project Delivery, Continuous Improvement, SPSS software, and Qualtrics (data collection).

#### **Education & Certifications**

**BSc (Hons) Psychology** [with placement] Brunel University London Graduated 2021

Modules include:

Bio Psych (A), Statistics (B), & Clinical Psychology (B)

**Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate** Coursera September 2022 **Mobile Marketing** Google Digital Garage January 2022 **Fundamentals of Digital Marketing** Google Digital Garage January 2022 **Psychological First Aid** Coursera February 2021

# **Work Experience**

**Assistant Supervisor** Bandar Supermarket April 2022 - Current

Working at an independent family-run supermarket, butcher shop and cafe.

- Trained staff on health and safety, till use & cashing out.
- Managed incoming deliveries and completed quality control over inventory.
- Completed deliveries to our customers and carried out customer satisfaction reviews.
- Deputised for store manager on several occasions and ensured the store is maintained at all times.
- Produced ad hoc reports on product sales and income via Excel.

#### **Customer Service Assistant** M&S

August 2021 - Current

- Organised, labelled & processed over 100 items daily accommodating constantly changing shipping schedules & delivery times
- Demonstrated leadership and management abilities
- ➤ Contribute to store sales & cost control
- > Performed daily quality checks to ensure damaged items were recorded and removed
- Understand customer needs & spot selling opportunities
- Cashing out tills & handling thousands of pounds of cash daily and accurately recording.

**Team Member Star** Pret A Manger *Nov 2018 – Jan 2020* **Hot Chef** (Promotion) Jan 2020 -

August 2020

- Worked with a group of 5 team members to improve daily sales and breaking area records for the highest gross income on the weekend, by utilizing key performance indicators for hourly & weekly food sales.
- Responsible for producing the highest quality product and trained new colleagues on key aspects of the job.
- Received additional training in Health & Safety (including First Aid), COSHH handling as well as Barista training.

> Contributed ideas into multiple projects in the Centre for Culture and Evolution with a primary focus on the 'Infidelity Motivation' study.

> Conducted data analysis (SPSS, Qualtrics & Excel), designed experiments (via Gorilla), prepared ethics applications, edited research proposals, and contributed to research papers.

# Assistant Vocational Teaching Officer Bank Life Skills Practitioner

OPTIONS West London Community College

May 2019 – Jan 21 (Periodically)

Aug 2018 -Dec 2018

Worked one-on-one with adults who are living with autism alongside, learning disability, depression, anxiety, muscle dystrophy, fragile X and reduced communication skills. I assisted the speech and language therapist in implementing therapeutic techniques.

- Basic Makaton (simplified sign language)
- ➤ Leading life skills sessions (including maths and road safety)
- > Risk management
- Planning
- Daily/Monthly evaluation of progress

During this time, I further enhanced my skills by completing a 'Care Certificate Standard Level 1'